[Music]
what if there's a better way to boost
your life protection and finances
what if you can get up to 60 times more
life protection coverage for what you
set aside
wouldn't it be great to have a plan that
grows your funds faster introducing
manulife future boost an affordable life
insurance plan that comes with built-in
investments designed to hustle with you
and reward you with bonuses
so you can feel secure at every stage of
your life see how this plan can boost
your life goals and finances
you can pay as low as 20 000 pesos and
space your payments out over 5 or 10
years you'll then get life protection
worth up to 60 times what you paid boost
your coverage further through optional
add-ons
choose to invest in a variety of
expertly managed funds that give you
access to both local and global growth
opportunities
for the third to ten years of your
policy if you consistently pay on time
you can get extra five percent on your
yearly premium this automatically gets
added to your plan's investment value
positive movements in the investment
market plus your premium bonuses will
help increase your plan's investment
value further if you choose to add more
funds to your policy beyond your
selected payment term you can look
forward to receiving additional two
percent in bonuses each time you pay
that can give your earning potential an
extra boost and after 10 years future
boost will start rewarding you every
year for your loyalty
apart from these value adding bonuses
you may also choose to increase your
coverage any time to adjust to changes
in your life stage and protection needs
blast off towards a secure future with
future boost
let manulife take you on a faster ride
towards reaching your life goals and
priorities so you can live every day
better
[Music]
you